betfairfootball.com 2019-11-16

# Betfair

Your personal information may be transferred or disclosed to any company within the Group or, subject to appropriate agreement, to third parties, for the processing of that personal information based on our instructions and in compliance with this policy and any other appropriate confidentially and security measures.

### Within the Group:

Any reference to the "Group" within this Policy includes Flutter Entertainment plc and all or any of its direct or indirect subsidiary undertakings, joint venture partners, and their related companies wherever located in the world as may exist from time to time including, but not limited to, Paddy Power, Betfair, , Timeform, Sportsbet, FanDuel, Draft, TVG and Adjarabe. Any member of Flutter Entertainment plc may use and share, within the group and with its advisors, the information you provide and other information it holds about you for the following purposes:

  * Account set up, verification and management;
  * Marketing and events
  * Risk management; and 
  * Legal and regulatory obligations.

### Our third-party service providers & partners: 

The Group may, from time to time, retain trusted third parties to process your information to provide us with services globally, including for customer support, information technology, payments, sales, marketing, data analysis, research and surveys. As part our agreements with our partners, we may be required to share your information for the purposes of calculating fees and benefits owed.

### Third parties for legal reasons:

We will share personal information when we believe it is required, such as:

  * To comply with legal obligations and respond to requests from government agencies, including law enforcement and other public authorities, which may include such authorities outside your country of residence;
  * In the event of a merger, sale, restructure, acquisition, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings); and
  * To protect our rights, users, systems, and Services.

### Regulatory or Sporting body

Your personal information including, but not limited to, your registration details, betting records, records of payments, device information etc., may also be disclosed to any regulatory or sporting body (with whom the Group has agreements (Memoranda of Understanding or "MOUs") for the sharing of such data) in connection with policing the integrity or enforcing the rules of a sport or game and/or prevention and detection of crime and where the Group considers that there are reasonable grounds to suspect that you may be involved in a breach of such rules or the law, have knowledge of a breach of such rules or the law or otherwise pose a threat to the integrity of the relevant sport or game based upon our assessment of your betting behaviours or it may be based on information provided to us by a regulatory or sporting body. Those bodies may then use your personal information to investigate and act on any such breaches in accordance with their procedures.

### International Transfers

Flutter Entertainment plc operates businesses in multiple jurisdictions some of which are not located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”). Countries outside the EEA do not always have strong data protection laws. Where we transfer personal information from the EEA to other countries in which applicable laws do not offer the same level of data privacy protection as in your home country, we take measures to provide an appropriate level of data privacy protection. For example, we use approved contractual clauses, intragroup agreements and other measures designed to ensure that the recipients of your personal information protect it. We take steps to ensure that the information we collect is processed according to this privacy policy and the requirements of the applicable law wherever the data is located. Please contact us below if you require further information.
